《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously, on AMC's The Walking Dead.
我们有人手和武器
We have people, and weapons.
如果我们联盟  先下手为强  就能打败他们
If we strike first, together, we can beat them.
会死人
People will die.
会死很多人  不仅是救世军
A lot of people, and not just the Saviors.
如果能找到更好的办法  必须找到
If we can find another way, we have to.
知道如何打架  不意味着你应该去找茬
Just because you now know how to fight, doesn't mean you should seek one.
你只用说服以西结带领神之国反抗
You'll just have to convince Ezekiel to bring The Kingdom to fight.
不  我不想参与这事
No, this is something I am not a part of.
看上去少了
Ah, it looks light.
也许你该再看看  加文
Perhaps you might look again, Gavin.
我们履行了义务
We've met our obligations.
该死
God damn it.
醒醒  孩子
Wake it up, kid.
为什么非得这么早
Why does it have to be so early?
今天有很多事要做
Got a lot to do today.
你想继续睡觉吗
You want to go back to sleep?
不想
No way.
你刚来找我的时候
You said you wanted to be able to knock your brother
说想打败你哥哥
on his butt when you first came to me.
你真想这样吗
That really what you want?
是啊
Yeah.
不是
No.
你想跟你哥哥一样
You want to be like your brother.
对吗
Yeah?
对
Yeah. ?
好吧
All right.
检查你的步法
Check your feet,
-如果你的步法错  -一切都错
- 'cause if your feet ain't right -- - Nothing's right.
我们正打算出去清理...
We were just about to come out to clear the --
摩根在哪
Where's Morgan?
-你没事吧  -摩根在哪
- You okay? - Where is Morgan?
为什么耶稣带达里尔和其他人来神之国
Why did Jesus bring Daryl and everyone else to the Kingdom?
他们
They, um...
他们想看看我们能不能一起合作
They wanted to see if we could all start working together on things.
救世军还在
The Saviors are still here.
他们没跟神之国打仗  但是
They're not fighting with the Kingdom, but...
达里尔说他们在亚历山大打败了救世军
Daryl said they beat them back in Alexandria.
是真的吗
Is that true?
他们达成了协议吗
That they made a deal with them?
大家都还好吗
Is everyone okay?
告诉我是不是真的
Just tell me if it's true.
你得去问达里尔
You need to talk to Daryl about that.
你让我不告诉所有人你的事
You wanted me to keep the whole story about you from everybody.
让我不说你在哪
Told me not to say where you were,
我照你的吩咐做了
and I did what you asked.
达里尔不是靠我找到你的
Daryl didn't find you because of me.
你俩之间说的话
And what was said between you and him
是你俩的事
was said between you and him.
我会跟你去亚历山大
I will go with you to Alexandria,
如果你想去
if you want to make the trip...
如果你想跟他谈
if you want to talk to him.
你不该一个人去
You shouldn't go alone.
你找到了想要的  对吧
You found what you wanted, right?
你逃开了所有人
You got away from everyone.
那是你想要的吗
Is it what you wanted?
还是太迟  已经没法逃离了
Was it just too late to get away?
我们现在就能去亚历山大
Hey, we can leave for Alexandria right now.
如果你想的话
Right now, if you want to.
我能帮你什么忙吗
Is there anything I can help you with?
-不能  -我能不能
- No. - ?Well, can I just --
如果你不介意  我可以送你回小屋吗
If you don't mind, could I walk back to the cottage with you?
不行
No!
我们今天要上贡  但我可以不去
We have a drop today, but I can miss it.
我只是
I just...
我在努力学习
I'm trying to learn,
看到了你之前做的事  我...
and seeing what you did here, I...
有五个行尸
There were five of them.
如果你能让我看看
I would just really appreciate it
你是怎么做到的  我会很感激
if you would just...let me see how you do what you do.
不行  去上贡吧
No. Go do your drop.
好吧
Okay.
凯蒂
准你上前  娜比拉
You may approach, Nabila.
我待在原地就好
I'm fine where I am.
希瓦喜欢你
Shiva likes you.
我就怕它喜欢我
That's what I'm afraid of.
告诉我你发现了什么
Tell me what you found.
你不会喜欢的
You're not gonna like it.
我更不喜欢被坏消息吊胃口
I like waiting to hear bad news less.
我们遇到了个小问题
We got a little problem
但它一周之内就可能变成大问题
that could turn into a big problem inside of a week.
下面大部分植物都生了象鼻虫
Most of the plants down there, they got weevils.
我们必须把它们全部剪了烧掉
We have to cut and burn everything
不然会蔓延到院子里的主要农作物上
before the weevils get to the main crops in the courtyard.
我知道皇家花园对你而言很重要
I know the Royal Garden is important to you.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
谢谢你  娜比拉
Thank you, Nabila.
该怎么办就怎么办吧
Do what must be done.
陛下  美妙之处就在于...
Here's the beautiful thing, Your Majesty --
你可以把它们拔了剪了
you can tear it out and cut it down.
你可以把它们烧了扔掉
You can burn it and throw it all away.
但如果你想的话  它们还会再长回来
But if you want, it can all grow back.
好吧  我觉得我尿裤子了
Okay. I think I just pissed myself.
我得走了
I'm-a gonna go.
五分钟后出发
We're at "five minutes go."
好
Okay.
谢谢你给了我这本书
Thank you for this.
我还在思考
I'm still thinking about it.
"伤害敌人就是伤害自己"
"To injure an opponent is to injure oneself."
无论如何都会受伤是吧
Get injured no matter what.
我给你带了件礼物  放在你新家的
I got something for you -- for the new place.
谢了
Thanks.
我出去找物资时在一家餐厅里发现的
I found it at a restaurant I was scavenging.
我认识一个女孩  她帮我把它修好了
I know a girl, and she, uh, fixed it up for me.
瞧
There.
我正好看那钉子看烦了呢
I was getting tired of looking at that nail.
那个女孩是谁
So, who's the girl?
我们还有三分钟就要出发了
We're at, like, "three minutes go" right now,
所以...
so...
那孩子小小年纪就得当爹
Kid's too young to be a father.
你当过爹吗
Were you one?
当过  谢天谢地
I was, thank God.
但我那时可不小
But I wasn't too young --
完美的年纪  完美的时间
perfect age, perfect time.
我有完美的家庭和完美的人生
I had myself the perfect family and the perfect life.
我所求不多  得到的却超过预期
I didn't ask for much, and I got more than I deserved.
你呢
And you?
很抱歉我俩之间有些不快
I'm sorry for how things have been between you and me.
我觉得你对杀戮的看法是错的
I think you're wrong about killing...
觉得我们能和救世军长期共处的想法也是错的
about how you think things can last like this with the Saviors.
但我还是得道歉
But I'm sorry.
我知道你是个好人
I know you're a good man.
但总有一天  你不能再这样好下去
The day's coming where you can't be that good.
等到那时
When that happens,
别为此自责
don't beat yourself up about it.
本杰明  我们该出发了
Benjamin, it's time for us to take our leave.
再见  小伙子
See you, little man.
把馅饼放下
Leave the cobbler.
真要这样吗
Really?
杰瑞
Jerry.
好吧
Fine.
那女孩是谁
Who's the girl?
大家都别动  把枪端好
Everyone stay down. Get your guns up.
有人把路堵上了
Somebody blocked the road.
一定不是什么好事
Can't be for anything good.
陛下  留在车里
Your Majesty, stay inside.
如果你们想的话就下来看看
Take a look if you want,
但把枪都端好了
but keep your guns up.
梯队向右
Echelon right.
向那栋楼行进
Force towards the building over there.
迪恩家电维修
大家围着国王
Let's close around the king.
我来掩护
I got cover.
我们到那栋楼去
Let's move towards the building.
本杰明  把枪端起来
Benjamin, get your gun up.
端得够高了吗
Think that's high enough?
你做得挺好的  伙计
You're fine, man.
葬我于此
天啊
Jesus...
这个世界把人逼疯了
This world drives one mad.
人们经历了各种苦难
People have lived through every kind of misery...
暴君  种族灭绝  仇恨制度
tyrants, genocide, systems of quiet hate...
而别人却在同一块土地上享受着自由
while others enjoy freedom on the same piece of land.
然而如今  我们唯有这样生存
Yet this, how we must exist now...
没全都被逼疯仅仅是走运
It is mere luck we are not all insane.
这不是走运  陛下
It isn't luck, Your Majesty.
怎讲
How's that?
这世界确实把人逼疯了
The world does drive people crazy now.
但是
But...
你为我们创造了新世界
you made us another world.
你们迟到了
You're late.
希望你能原谅  我们在路上...
If you could indulge us your pardon, our path...
我不想听
I don't want to hear about it.
别打断国王
Don't interrupt the king.
你个獐头鼠目的混蛋
You rat-faced prick.
以西结  这里没有国王
Ezekiel, there aren't any kings,
总统或首相
presidents, or prime ministers.
那些都是童话故事了
And all that is a fairy tale, too.
别在我们面前玩"陛下"那一套
Don't bring that "Your Highness" Shit our way.
很感谢你们一直上贡  但是
Now, I appreciate that you've been delivering, but...
气氛总是不必要的紧张
things have been unnecessarily tense,
所以我也不必要的紧张
and that makes me unnecessarily tense.
我来办这事不是找压力的
I didn't go this route for stress.
不  我是来放松的
No. Just the opposite.
那么进入正题  今天的贡品带了吗
So let's get to it. Do you have today's offering?
你们的枪我也要
I want your guns, too.
协议可没有这条
We did not agree to that.
你们有个选择
Well, you got a choice...
我猜一开始你们就有这个选择
Same one that's been there since the beginning, I guess.
你们可以交出枪
You can give up your guns,
或者开枪试试
or you can try to use them.
选哪个
What's it gonna be?
我们应该交枪  陛下
We should give them over, Your Majesty.
"Ehh, we should give 'em over, Your Majesty".
或许我应该用棍子捅穿你喉咙
Or maybe I'll just shove this down your throat.
把棍子还给摩根
Give Morgan his stick back.
枪就给你们
Then you can have the guns.
-然后大家各奔东西  -以西结
- And all of us can go on with our day's journeys. - Ezekiel...
我需要你明白现在这种局面的严重性
I need you to understand the gravity of what's happening here.
我给了你选择
I gave you a choice.
你选哪个
What is it going to be?
选吧
Come on.
你知道该选哪个
You know the answer.
算了
It's fine.
枪给他们
Give them your guns.
我们拿走你们的枪
We took your guns just now
是因为你们马上会动感情
because things are about to get emotional.
据以往的经验
You guys have proven
你们一感情用事  就搞砸事情
that you don't do so good with emotional.
贡品不够
You're short.
我们要十二颗  这只有十一颗
We said 12. I count 11.
是十二颗
There are 12 there.
-不是  -再数一遍
- There aren't. - Count again.
你来数
You count them!
我数过的
I counted them.
我数过  这不可能
I did. T-This is impossible.
有可能
It's possible.
是真的
It's real.
就发生在眼前
It's happening now.
而现在  问题必须解决
And the problems have to end...now.
你们必须明白代价
You have to learn the stakes here,
我们得教教你们
so we're gonna teach you.
你们不用动手
You don't have to do anything.
一小时之内我们会送来双倍贡品
We'll get you twice the tribute in an hour.
现在
Right now...
是唯一重要的时间
is the only time that matters.
而现在
And right now...
你们没有履行义务
you haven't held up your side of the bargain.
在我们谈了
After we have talked about things,
一遍又一遍之后
over and over again and again.
我们只能做个了结
So we're gonna deal with all of this...
就现在
right now.
现在  是字面意思的"现在"吗
Right now as in..."right now"?
是的
Yeah.
现在
Right...now.
动手吧
Just do it.
好吧
Okay.
不
No!
大家都别动
Everybody settle down!
我们得把本杰明带回神之国
We need to get Benjamin back to the Kingdom.
把那人的棍子还他
Give the man his damn stick!
滚回车里去  一个字都别说
Get in the truck! Don't say a goddamn word!
-我们得回去  -不行
- We need to get back. ?- No.
现在  你们都得听好了
Right now, you have to listen.
就这一次  给我听仔细了
For once, be present and listen.
以后  你们必须每一次
You will make your deliveries on time,
都按时送货  不能少一分
every time, and they will be complete.
要么优秀要么不及格  没有未完成
It's A's or F's, no I's.
明天把你们欠的贡品送过来
You are gonna show me that you understand
向我证明你们懂我的意思了
by bringing the balance of what you owe tomorrow.
我们得马上走  他会流血身亡的
We need to go! He's bleeding out!
一颗甜瓜  不多不少
One cantaloupe, not more, not less!
明白了吗
Do you understand?!
明白了
Yes, I understand.
-去处理他的伤口吧  -好
- Go patch him up. - Okay.
戴安  我们得带他去卡萝尔那里
Dianne, we need to drive to Carol's!
我们给了她很多医疗用品
We loaded her up with medical supplies!
得赶快止住他的血
We need to stop the bleeding.
他撑不到回神之国了
He's not gonna make it to the Kingdom.
走吧
Let's go!
上来
Up!
上车啊
Get in!
坚持住  坚持住
Stay with me. Stay with me.
我就在这  坚持住
I'm right here. Stay with me.
-好了  没事  -没事的
- All right. Okay. - It's okay.
没事的
It's okay.
"伤害敌人
"T-To injure an opponent...
就是伤害自己"
is to injure yourself.
很抱歉过来打搅你
I'm sorry for coming to you.
我们实在没办法了
We had no choice.
摩根  等等
Morgan, wait.
好了
Okay.
天啊
Oh, God.
葬我于此
清醒
别靠近我
Stay away from me.
听着就好
Just listen.
葬我于此
听着就好
不  不
No! No! Aah!
我知道
I know!
不  不  不
No! No! No!
我知道
I know!
够了  不
Enough! No!
本杰明  把枪端起来
Benjamin, get your gun up.
本来死的人该是我
It was supposed to be me.
加文说过
That's what Gavin said --
我会是第一个
that I'd be first.
我本想阻止的
I was trying to stop it.
我本想献出自己的性命来警醒你们
I was gonna give my life to show you!
今天本该那样的
That's what should've happened today.
我是那样试着做的
That's what I tried.
但是发生了意料之外的事
And something else happened
因为我们没有做什么去阻止他们
because we have done nothing to stop them.
我们什么都没做
We've done nothing!
没做
Nothing.
灾变发生时我在一个营地
I was in a camp when it started.
无边无际的大营
It was huge...endless...
到处是帐篷  茅厕
a city of -- of tarps and latrines
炊烟  婴儿的哭声
and wood smoke and babies crying.
总有婴儿的哭声
There were always babies crying.
我知道情况不妙
I knew they had problems,
但我不觉得轮得到我来管
but I didn't think they were mine to solve.
我以为比我有能力比我聪明的人会管
I thought there were stronger or smarter people there than me.
我算什么呢
W-Who the hell am I, right?
所以我什么都没做
So I did nothing.
之后有一场战斗
A-And there was a fight...
起了火
and a fire.
我失去了妻子
And I lost my wife.
三天没有食物  没有睡觉
And after three days of running,
恐怖骇人的
no food, and no sleep...
逃命后
of horror and terror...
我失去了女儿
I lost my little girl.
就在我面前...
Right in front of me...
因为我什么都没做
because I didn't do something.
因为我干等
Because I waited.
听我说
Listen to me.
拜托
Please.
听着就好
Just listen.
我们可以利用这事
We can use what's happened.
我们可以向救世军表明我们吸取了教训
We can show the Saviors that we get it.
我们明白要做什么
We understand what we need to do.
我们知道怎么继续下去
We know how to go on.
他们要相信我们
And they need to believe us.
我们必须得做点什么使他们相信
We have to do something to make them believe us.
等我们赢回他们的信任后
And then, when we gain their trust back...
再杀了他们
we kill them...
一了百了
end them.
我们加入亚历山大和山顶寨的同盟
We join with Alexandria and the Hilltop,
一举歼灭他们
and we crush them in one fell swoop.
但你得接受事实  摩根
But this is it, Morgan.
你必须要杀戮
You have...to...kill.
不然你还不如自杀
Or else you might as well just kill yourself.
总得有人死
Someone had to die.
我曾想成为那个人  但没有成功
I tried to be the one. That didn't happen.
所以我要成为领导我们的军队
So I'll be the one to lead our army
去粉碎救世军的人  摧毁他们
to crush the Saviors -- destroy them.
我
Me.
我会和以西结说
I'll talk to Ezekiel.
我会告诉所有人我做的事
I'll tell everyone what I did.
然后我会用余生去弥补
And I'll live the rest of my life making up for it.
你告诉他了吗
Did you tell him?
有吗
Did you?
现在不行
Not now.
我们回去再说
We'll talk about it when we get back.
什么事
What is it?
最好我们回去再说  陛下
It's better to talk about it when we get back, Your Majesty.
现在就说
We'll talk about it now.
那孩子怎么样
How's the kid?
他死了
He's dead.
在我杀了你之前快滚
Start walking back now before I kill you.
你多说一句  多瞟一眼
You say one word or throw one look,
我就地杀了你
I'll kill you right here and now.
滚
Go!
东西拿了吗
Do you have it?
我只想说  我们明白了
I just want to say we get it.
我们懂了
We understand.
-住手  -别管
- Cease this! - Leave 'em be!
摩根  住手
Morgan! Stop!
摩根
Morgan!
都是他搞的鬼
He set it all up.
他昨天挡路  让我们迟到
He blocked the road yesterday, made us late.
都是他干的
It was all him.
我们离开时  贡品还在
And we had your offering when we left --
全都在
had it all.
他从里面拿走了一颗  藏了起来
He took one from the cargo, and he hid it --
在我们停车时
when we stopped.
他想挑起神之国和救世军的争端
He wanted to get something started between the Kingdom and the Saviors.
我想让你看到...
Wanted to show you...
我想让你看到我们吸取了教训
Wanted to show you that we get it...
我们明白要做什么
That we understand what it is that we need to do --
我们知道怎么继续下去
that we know how to go on.
很好
Good.
下周  同一时间
Next week, same time.
我们明白
We -- We understand.
是他干的
He -- He did this?
他之前就想为我们死
He wanted to die for us before.
他希望死的是自己
He wanted it to be him.
他以为自己有的选  所以德韦恩才死了
Thought he could choose, and that's why Duane had to die.
"德韦恩"
"Duane"?
本杰明  所以本杰明才...
Benjamin -- Benjamin -- That's why Benjamin...
摩根
Morgan...
我们走吧
let us take our leave.
我本来就打算走
I was supposed to.
摩根  你不能一个人待在外面
Morgan, you should not be alone here.
走吧
Go.
现在不行
Not now.
-本杰明不想...  -我说了现在不行
- Benjamin not -- would not - ?Man, I said not now!
我说了...
I said...
你们走吧
Y'all just go.
凯蒂
你真想知道亚历山大发生了什么吗
Do you really want to know what happened in Alexandria?
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我杀了理查德
Killed Richard.
掐死了他
I strangled him.
他害死了本杰明  所以...
He's the one got Benjamin killed, so...
你想知道亚历山大发生了什么吗
Do you want to know what happened in Alexandria?
想
Yeah.
尼根杀了格伦和亚伯拉罕
Negan killed Glenn and Abraham.
什么
What?
用棒球棍活活打死了他们
Beat them to death with a baseball bat.
现在救世军统治着亚历山大  瑞克和其他人...
Now the Saviors have Alexandria, and Rick and everybody else...
都得为救世军做事
everything they do is for the Saviors now.
他们还杀了更多人
And they killed more.
杀了斯宾塞  奥利维亚
Killed Spencer, Olivia...
耶稣带瑞克一伙人来是因为
Jesus brought Rick and the rest here because...
瑞克想反抗他们
Rick wants to fight them.
是你想知道的
You wanted to know.
现在你知道了
Now you do.
-你去哪  -我去杀他们
- Where are you going? - I'm gonna kill them --
在外面  一个个杀
out there, one by one.
-但是去哪  -别的地方
- But where? ? - Somewhere else.
等等
W-Wait.
Wait. Just wait. Wait!
你可以走  同时也不走
You can go...and not go.
拜托了
Please.
单行道
卡萝尔
Carol.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
谢谢
I thank you.
我会住在这里
I'm gonna be here now.
我们要做准备
We have to get ready.
我们必须反抗
We have to fight.
是的
We do.
但不在今天
But not today.
行尸走肉
『第七季  第十三集』
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻译     冰蓝 Reginamoon CS小明漫画家
翻译     凉粉 小僵僵 送小孩
校对     送小孩
时间轴     某雪  加森
后期     送小哥  拉图
总监     送小孩